<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>🔊 Audio &#8211; Pine Close CMS</title>
	<atom:link href="http://192.168.0.108/tag/%F0%9F%94%8A-audio/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://192.168.0.108</link>
	<description>content management system</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 23:03:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Loud music, banging and yelling. &#124; 1st April 2023</title>
		<link>http://192.168.0.108/01apr2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[no#15]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Audio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[WDH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[🔊 Audio]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.0.108/?p=66</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Summery: on the 1st April 2023, we were woken up to Loud music, banging, stomping around and yelling. Reported To:&#46;&#46;&#46;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Summery:<br />
</strong>on the 1st April 2023, we were woken up to Loud music, banging, stomping around and yelling.</p>
<p><strong>Reported To:</strong><br />
This was the first time we felt the need to log a complaint with WDH regarding number 14, we tried to talk with him but we got ignored, even laughed at through the window when knocking at the door.</p>
<p><strong>Key Points:<br />
</strong>Very Tired, Very Stressed, Brother and sister unable to sleep before collage on multiple occasions (they no longer come round), Lucy has stress chest pain</p>
<p><strong>Details:<br />
</strong>We were kept awake all night because of the noise, and at the time Michael&#8217;s Brother &amp; Sister were staying round for the night, this caused a lot of stress, every time they stop round they cant sleep and are made jump by random bangs every time.<br />
This is after we attempted to contact them the week prior to this because they did the exact same thing then.<br />
We posted them a professionally worded letter kindly requesting that they keep the noise down a little at night, including that we have family round sometimes who have collage the day after sometimes, and that Lucy has 2 heart conditions and can not be made to jump or get scared, which has been completely ignored, and worse over time.<br />
We also attempted to speak to them by knocking on the door that night 3 times, all of which we were ignored, and they definitely heard us because the dog was balking very loud every time, and the 3rd time we went to knock, the tenant of number 14 and his friend were staring at us and laughing.<br />
We contacted WDH via OneCall and some how ended up working with the Environment Agency from there for a few months before being put through to the correct department of WDH</p>
<p><strong>Audio: </strong>Recording of loud music heard in every room<br />
<span style="font-size: 10pt;"><em>      Recorded on Microsoft Lumia 960 Phone</em></span><br />
<video controls="controls" width="480" height="32"><source src="/audio/1st%20April%202023%20-%20loud%20music.mp3" type="video/mp4" /></video></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
