<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>example &#8211; Pine Close CMS</title>
	<atom:link href="http://192.168.0.108/category/example/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://192.168.0.108</link>
	<description>content management system</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 04:44:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Typical Activity Example &#124; 10th May 2025</title>
		<link>http://192.168.0.108/10may2025/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[no#15]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 05:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[example]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[📹 Video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.0.108/?p=954</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Summery: On May 10th, 2025, routine yet frequent foot traffic and activity were observed around Flat Number 14. Throughout the&#46;&#46;&#46;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Summery:<br />
</strong>On<strong> May 10th</strong>, <strong>2025</strong>, routine yet frequent foot traffic and activity were observed around Flat Number 14. Throughout the day, two individuals-a male in a grey hoodie with camouflage trousers and a shirtless male (later seen wearing a shirt)-were repeatedly seen approaching Flat 14’s door and lingering in the vicinity. Notably, both individuals frequently looked at Flat Number 15’s door, bins, and camera, often pausing to observe these areas as they moved about.<br />
While it is not standard practice for us to log daily foot traffic, this report serves as an example of the typical activity and comings and goings associated with Flat 14, where various individuals are regularly seen entering, exiting, and loitering near the premises.</p>
<p><strong>Reported To:</strong><br />
Logged on this CMS</p>
<p><strong>Details and Timeline:<br />
</strong>On<strong> May 10th</strong>, <strong>2025</strong>, throughout the day<strong>,<br />
</strong><strong>05:10 AM:</strong> Male wearing a grey hoodie (hood up) and camouflage trousers approached Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>05:11 AM:</strong> The same individual (grey hoodie) left, walking past the front camera.<br />
<strong>05:34 AM:</strong> Grey hoodie male returned and again went to Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>05:35 AM:</strong> Grey hoodie male left, passing the front camera.<br />
<strong>08:25 AM:</strong> Resident of Flat 14 exited the building, wearing a cap, black track pants, black jacket, and a backpack.<br />
<strong>09:01 AM:</strong> Resident of Flat 14 returned, captured via the side camera.<br />
<strong>11:08 AM:</strong> Shirtless male (previously seen on May 9th, 2025) walked towards Flat 14’s door, captured on the front camera.<br />
<strong>11:09 AM:</strong> Shirtless male appeared on the side camera.<br />
<strong>11:09 AM:</strong> Shirtless male appeared again on the side camera.<br />
<strong>11:11 AM:</strong> Shirtless male appeared on the side camera.<br />
<strong>11:11 AM:</strong> Shirtless male observed walking around outside, pacing back and forth to Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>11:12 AM:</strong> Shirtless male appeared on the side camera.<br />
<strong>11:12 AM:</strong> Shirtless male continued pacing back and forth outside.<br />
<strong>11:13 AM:</strong> Shirtless male appeared again on the side camera.<br />
<strong>11:14 AM:</strong> Shirtless male observed walking around, swinging his shirt.<br />
<strong>11:15 AM:</strong> Shirtless male walked around, then returned towards Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>11:19 AM:</strong> Shirtless male continued walking around, back and forth.<br />
<strong>11:20 AM:</strong> Shirtless male continued walking around, then returned.<br />
<strong>11:20 AM:</strong> Shirtless male stood at the grass edge on his phone while walking around, then moved off camera towards Flat 14.<br />
<strong>11:22 AM:</strong> Shirtless male continued walking around while on his phone.<br />
<strong>11:23 AM:</strong> Shirtless male, still on the phone and swinging his shirt, was joined by the resident of Flat 14; both stood at the curb talking. Shirtless male then walked away, and the resident returned to Flat 14.<br />
<strong>12:33 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male (same as earlier) returned to Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>12:35 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male walked away, carrying something in his hand.<br />
<strong>04:58 PM:</strong> Resident of Flat 14 walked away, passing the front camera.<br />
<strong>05:34 PM:</strong> Resident of Flat 14 walked past, checking behind him and looking at the reporting party’s door, followed by the shirtless male (from earlier and the previous day).<br />
<strong>05:35 PM:</strong> Shirtless male observed outside, looking at the bins and front door area while walking around smoking. He moved off camera, then returned near the reporting party’s door, appeared to talk to the resident of Flat 14, then left toward Flat 14’s bins and exited past the front camera.<br />
<strong>05:36 PM:</strong> Resident of Flat 14 went to a white car parked on the corner, spoke to the driver, made arm motions, then walked back towards his door, waved the car off, and went back inside.<br />
<strong>05:55 PM:</strong> Shirtless male, now wearing a shirt, was seen looking at Flat 14’s window.<br />
<strong>06:24 PM:</strong> Shirtless male stood on the grass, looking up at Flat 14’s window.<br />
<strong>06:25:53 PM:</strong> Shirtless male walked to the curb, then back to Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>06:26 PM:</strong> Shirtless male stood on the grass, looking around and up at the window again.<br />
<strong>06:27 PM:</strong> Shirtless male stood looking at the reporting party’s door and then at his phone, before leaving past the bins.<br />
<strong>06:28 PM:</strong> Shirtless male returned, went to Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>06:28 PM:</strong> Shirtless male, on his phone, looked at Flat 14’s window, then walked away past the bins while still on his phone.<br />
<strong>07:27 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male walked past towards Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>07:28 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male walked near the reporting party’s door, looked up at Flat 14’s window, then returned towards Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>08:28 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male reappeared on camera, looking at Flat 14’s bins and window.<br />
<strong>08:28 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male walked back, stared at Flat 14’s window again, then returned to Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>08:29 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male left, going past the bins.<br />
<strong>08:30 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male returned towards Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>08:48 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male left again, passing the bins.<br />
<strong>08:49 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male returned again to Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>09:03 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male walked away, passing the bins.<br />
<strong>09:04 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male returned again to Flat 14’s door.<br />
<strong>09:57 PM:</strong> Grey hoodie male left, walking back past the bins.</p>
<p><strong>Observations:<br />
*</strong> The grey hoodie male and shirtless male were regularly present throughout the day, demonstrating a consistent pattern of movement and interaction around Flat 14.<br />
<strong>* </strong>Both individuals frequently looked at and lingered near our door, bins, and camera, suggesting a heightened interest in our property.<br />
<strong>*</strong> The shirtless male’s presence on consecutive days suggests ongoing activity linked to Flat 14.<br />
<strong>*</strong> The general environment around Flat 14 is characterized by a high volume of visitors and transient individuals, with people regularly entering, exiting, and loitering near the property.<br />
<strong>*</strong> These behaviors appear to represent the typical foot traffic and activity associated with Flat 14 on this date.</p>
<p><strong>Video:</strong><strong><br />
</strong> <video controls="controls" width="600" height="340"><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><span style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><span style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><span style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><span style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span><source src="/videos/10may2025-720p-compressed.mp4" type="video/mp4" /><span style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_end">﻿</span><span style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_end">﻿</span><span style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_end"><span style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_start">﻿</span>﻿</span><span style="display: inline-block; width: 0px; overflow: hidden; line-height: 0;" data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_end">﻿</span><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_end">﻿</span><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_end">﻿</span><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_end">﻿</span><span data-mce-type="bookmark" class="mce_SELRES_end">﻿</span></video></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
